It summons magicite beasts.
Ripple!
I'm sorry!
I can't keep this up anymore!
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 9          A New Artifact
My desk!
It's huge!
Be careful, Rani!
It's probably as strong as Seilyn and Rahl
were when they became magicite beasts!
Your words and your face
are telling two different stories!
Oh, whoops.
It's a different color,
but I feel the same flow of power
as I did when I saw those heat rays.
Which means...
It's probably going to fire
heat rays everywhere!
S-Stop it, please!
Of course.
The cafeteria's on the floor below!
That's not what's important now!
Maybe I can't stop it firing, but...
She's so absurdly strong...
Sorry, ma'am.
I made a big hole in the roof.
W-Well, that's not so bad...
It's going to come back down, though.
We need Artifacts to
defeat a magicite beast.
It's going to land in the schoolyard!
When it does, I'll finish it off.
Wait!
Yua, it's dangerous there!
Above you! Above you!
Run away!
Chop!
Yua's amazing...
I may have already damaged it with my kick,
but she still managed to chop it in half
with a wave of her hand.
She's as strong as I thought!
Will we not see any more
magicite beasts for a while?
Yes. We learned in the last battle
that Ripple absorbs mana
from Special-class Rune bearers
and uses it to summon magicite beasts.
And summoning that magicite beast
drained the mana she'd built up.
We won't see another one until
her mana builds up again, right?
You understand well.
Um, I have another question.
Why do all the summoned magicite beasts
appear to be former demihumans?
Probably because Ripple
herself is a demihuman.
Demihumans have what you
might call a sixth sense.
It's said they could even use telepathy.
She's using that species-wide
connection to summon them.
Is that why?
Which is why what they did
could only be done to Ripple.
It's even possible they created a demihuman
Hyral Menas specifically for this purpose.
I feel bad for Ripple,
having her friends used in such a way.
A lot of Highlanders don't see people
on the surface as their equals,
which leads to this way of thinking.
It's embarrassing.
Now, now, everyone.
It's all in how you think about it!
My comrades have been stuck
as magicite beasts all this time,
so this way, we can finally let them rest.
As long as nobody around us gets hurt.
Of course! We'll make sure they don't!
Thanks, everyone.
Excuse me.
Come in!
Brother Raf!
Eris!
I've been worried about you.
Tell me how you're doing later.
Right now, we have urgent news.
Is something wrong, you two?
The neighboring country of Venefic
has violated our borders.
Prince Wein is asking for Sir Theodore
to return to the castle immediately.
Two Weeks Later
What a great bath!
I'm glad nothing happened
when we were on duty today!
I think one person here
would disagree with you.
We haven't seen a single
magicite beast since then!
That's a good thing!
You're right, but...
Don't you think we need a place where
we can show off the results of our training?
I don't think that, no.
It's better for Ripple that nothing happens.
I get that, but...
Liselotte, have you heard
what's going on near the border?
There's a standoff going on right now,
I heard. But nothing beyond that...
So the Prismer's still not
doing anything either, huh?
That's the kind of sigh you make
when the one you like won't notice you.
Well, Chris does say her
ideal type is a Prismer.
It always feels like Chris is a totally
different person on the inside and outside.
Yes.
Her body is Boobs, but her brain is Muscles.
Yua!
I couldn't even sense her approach.
Impressive!
Wait...
If there aren't any magicite beasts...
Yua!
The way you chopped that magicite
beast in half was amazing!
I'd love it if you could
show me how it was done!
In a battle, preferably!
I refuse.
Why?
I don't like physical exercise.
Well, it's hard for me to respond to that...
What can I do to make you tell me?
Yua?
There's something I want you
to teach me, too.
If you do, I'll fight you,
or do anything else you want.
Really?
What is it?
I'll teach you anything you want to know!
How can I get my boobs that big, too?
Um, well... mine kinda just grew this way.
That doesn't tell me anything.
I want to have huge boobs
so everyone likes me!
I want to show off my cleavage
to the entire world, like you do, Boobs!
I don't do that!
If you can teach me a way
to make my breasts bigger,
I'll fight you as much as you want!
Leone!
I-I don't know either!
Plus, they're heavy, they make your
shoulders stiff, and people stare!
There's nothing good about them.
You're lucky you get
to worry about that stuff!
You don't know how us flat girls live!
So Rafinha's taking Yua's side?
You don't have to worry,
because you've got proper boobs.
And they're not big enough
to strain your shoulders.
In a way, they're the best size.
I don't know about that...
And you don't have to deal with
Lyn playing around in there.
I think Liselotte ought to
experience that at least once.
Go, Lyn!
N-No! It tickles!
Hey!
Somebody help me!
Liselotte was really mad...
She was intense. I was scared.
Rafinha!
I have something to give to you!
Change into your uniform and come
to the principal's office, would you?
Theodore says this is for you.
I this a new Artifact?
Yes. It has the same base as
your current "Shiny Flow,"
but it's an upgraded version
with a second Gift as well.
Wow! Thank you!
I'm surprised Theodore has any time to make
Artifacts, with how busy he is right now,
but this is a great help!
Yes!
Also, the second power that
Artifact has is one of healing.
I've never heard of an Artifact
with that kind of power!
It's quite rare and difficult to make.
That's why he wants you to have it, he says.
Theodore...
He also asks that you take care
of Ripple for him.
Of course!
I'll protect Ripple and everyone else!
I'll have to start training right now
so that I can use it properly!
Sure you do.
Chris, you always make that face
whenever Theodore is involved!
I am not making a face.
That's...
Hurry and put out the fire!
The magicite beast has been defeated.
The flames need putting out, now!
What's going on?
Principal Miliera!
Ripple summoned more magicite beasts.
We sealed them in a pocket space
and fought them, but...
Silva!
Silva?
He's horribly wounded...
I'm fine.
Forget about me, and get Ripple out of here.
I can't let her see me like this.
Make sure she's safe!
Okay!
For someone as strong as you
to be this badly injured...
It must have been a powerful
magicite beast indeed.
I'm so sorry... It was my failure.
No! It's not your fault!
It's their fault!
"Their fault"?
I'm sorry...
Rati... Pram?
What happened?
He protected me when a magicite
beast was about to kill me...
and he was badly hurt.
N-No! Rati tried to protect me!
So it's my fault!
I'm so sorry!
"Sorry" won't cut it!
Thanks to you, Silva is...
Stop.
My lack of care when activating the pocket
space caused them to be caught up in it.
The mistake was all mine.
And as someone with power,
it's my job to protect
the powerless Runeless.
Were you hurt?
No. Not even a scratch.
I see.
Then...
Silva?
Silva! Silva!
Oh, no! We need to hurry and
get him to the medical room!
Wait!
I'll try and help.
The healing Gift...
Please, go ahead!
Okay!
You'll be okay.
You can do it, Rani.
Does anything feel "wrong"?
Yes.
That's good. It means that your power is
flowing to a different Gift than usual.
Please continue.
Focus on what lies just
beyond your fingertips.
Okay...
So this is the healing Gift...
The movements of the mana are so complex,
I don't think I could easily recreate it...
Now hold that light up to Silva.
Okay!
His wounds...
They're healing!
So the healing Gift places
a heavy strain on its user?
Then...
Rani. I'll help you.
I can't copy the mana the Gift uses.
But if I just create mana with
a wavelength similar to Rani's...
Chris?
Think you can do it?
Yeah! I can do a lot more now!
He's okay now, isn't he?
Thank you both.
Now, get him to the medical room.
Okay!
Thank you for saving Silva.
No... Anyone would have done the same.
Thanks, Chris! You were a huge help!
Are the two of you okay?
We're fine...
Really?
That's...
The super-spicy meal!
It's so spicy!
But it's good!
It sure wakes you up, huh?
Super-spicy food reminds me of home, though.
Where did you say you were from?
Alucard, in the north.
It's cold up there, so you eat
spicy food to warm yourself up.
So we're used to eating really spicy food.
It reminds us of home!
You want some too, then?
I'd love some, but... there's so much...
I'll give you some of mine.
Th-Thanks...
Give me some too, Inglis!
Sure thing!
No!
Why?
No indirect kisses!
Sure, sure. Got it.
You're just doing what Pram
tells you today, huh?
Well, I did kinda screw up yesterday.
I owe you guys a big thank-you, too.
No, it's not your fault!
You just tried to help me...
But I had to be saved
by somebody else instead!
I need to apologize to Silva.
I don't think he was mad, though.
Yeah. He was sticking up for you.
He was kind of a jerk when we first met,
so I thought he just hated squires.
Oh, I get it!
He must be one of those guys
who likes young boys!
That's why he was so kind to Rati!
Well?
That can't be right!
Yeah, I really can't handle any more rivals!
So why was he so harsh on me?
Cause you're a girl, Chris! Obviously!
He just likes young boys...
I'd prefer you didn't jump to
conclusions about people like that.
Silva?
Are you feeling better?
Yes. The scars are almost all gone, too.
That Gift of yours is incredible.
Um, I'm so sorry about yesterday.
We're really sorry.
Don't worry about it. It was
my mistake to begin with.
And in the end, you were
the ones who saved me.
Let me apologize for my rudeness
and thank you properly.
Thank you.
Not at all... I'm sorry we were such brats!
I'm sorry!
Now we've all apologized,
so we're even, right?
Yes.
Let's say that we are.
Okay, your turn's over, Rani.
My turn now.
We ate a whole lot!
Let's do our best to defend
Ripple this afternoon!
Sure, but since Silva and his group
defeated the magicite beast,
we won't see another for a while.
Chris...
They can't do this!
Come in!
Excuse us.
It's time for our shift to begin.
Thanks for coming.
Um. It sounds like something
had upset you...
Oh, I'm sorry. I couldn't help myself.
Actually, the Royal Guard sent a demand to us
that we turn Ripple over
to them for protection.
Why now, after everything?
They say they're sending Ripple back to the
Highland and getting a new Hyral Menas.
But... You can't replace her just
because she's a little sick...
That's treating her like
an object, not a person!
We will continue to keep
her safe at the academy.
Right?
But, Miliera, if you get into
a fight with the Royal Guard,
won't that cause problems for everyone?
Not in the least.
Protecting you is what we all want to do.
She's right!
Leave it to us!
Guys...
Prism Flow? Now of all times?
The magicite beasts don't care
what we've got going on in our lives.
What's the principal
going to do about Ripple?
She's sending a formal message to
Prince Wein, as a means of buying time.
That's why Rati and Pram
ran off in the Flying Gears.
The prince is away right now.
It's bad timing.
They were excited to make up
for their failure before, though.
What's wrong?
Bad timing...
Oh, well, there's nothing
we can do about the rain.
No, I mean the way the Royal Guard is
doing this when Prince Wein isn't around.
If somebody is pulling strings
behind the scenes...
Leone!
On it!
A lightning beast...
That's the power of my brother's Artifact!
Brother Leon!
Hey. It's been a long time, Leone.
Wait!
Somebody else is here.
Who's there?!
It can't be...
The Bloodchain Brigade!
Silva is
a rival,
too?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
That's
imposs-
ible!
Comic by Kuromura Moto